blizzardinternet.com 2019-03-16

# Privacy Policy - Blizzard Internet Marketing

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form on our website.

When you fill out a form, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, mailing address, or phone number.

**Customer Email Lists: Collection, Usage and Preference Options  
**  
By supplying us with your email address (while interacting with us, subscribing to our newsletter, or during an event, etc.), we will use that email address for marketing solicitations and ads. You can opt-out of these electronic communications at any time by following the instructions in our emails or by [contacting us](https://www.blizzardinternet.com/about/contact/).  
**  
****What Do We Use Your Information For?** **  
**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To improve our website  
– To improve customer service  
– To occasionally show you remarketing, display, search or other ads in various advertising platforms

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
– To send periodic emails

When you become a client, the email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do We Use Cookies?**

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Third-party service providers may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from your website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads.

You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising Opt-out Page. You may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics Opt-out Page. You may opt out of third party vendor use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-out Page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or the Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choice page at www.aboutads.info/choices. If the advertiser is not listed on that website, please contact us at the address below in order to opt-out.

For further information regarding Google’s privacy practices, please visit http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

**Online Behavioral Advertising**

 ****Blizzard uses third party vendors to display relevant ads on sites throughout the internet. Many times these third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on your interaction with us. For more information on how Online Behavioral Advertising works, please visit[www.aboutads.info/consumers.](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) Users may opt out of some, many, or all Online Behavioral Advertising targeting by visiting either or both of the following sites: [networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out…](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and/or [aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).  ****

 **Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Blizzard Internet Marketing, Inc.  
1001 Grand Ave., Suite 005  
Glenwood Springs, Colorado 81601  
United States  
info@BlizzardInternet.com  
970-928-7875
